

I'm a UX Designer with a focus on accessibility. Academic projects explored how to achieve positive experiences for neurodiverse users through accessibility, to facilitate independence. I'm a First-class Honours design graduate with a Master of Science degree in User Experience Engineering. I possess experience in user interface and experience design, user research, information data visualisation and front-end development. I have a strong business acumen acquired from expertise in the technology sector, making me confident in decision-making and presenting design rationale.

Education

MSc User Experience Engineering. Distinction

Goldsmiths, University of London

Sept. 2020 — Sept. 2021

BA (Hons) Information & Interface Design. First Class with Honours

University of the Arts London, London College of Communication

Sept. 2017 — Jul. 2020

Experience

UX/UI Designer Mendix

Apr. 2022 - Present

Mendix is a low-code platform that provides tools to build, test, deploy and iterate applications.

Multidisciplinary Designer Cyberdog

Aug. 2020 - Mar. 2022

Working as a multidisciplinary designer for Cyberdog places me at the centre of our small team. My day-to-day responsibilities can range from:

- Creating visual assets for all digital channels including email marketing, social media, app and website
- Development of site content and graphics by coordinating with marketing, event and PR teammates
- Assisting in post-production of images and videos for online use
- Suggesting creative solutions to drive engagement with content, conversion and brand experience
- Reviewing competitors and keeping up to date with the latest design trends
- Delivering results under tight deadlines in a fast-paced environment

Designer & Web Designer Kitayah Music

Feb. 2020 - Jan. 2022

Responsibilities include; providing designs for branded content across social media; image editing; website design and creation - front-end development; supporting marketing campaigns through the creation of website elements, social assets, landing pages and graphics.

I designed and coded the company website: www.kitayah.com

Scrum Master & Participant Global Design Studio

Dec. 2018

A collaborative workshop run across three countries, UK, Denmark & Australia. Focused on online collaboration through services Fuze, Slack and Appear.in to collaborate efficiently with teammates.

I was invited back in March 2020 to participate as a group leader/scrum master, supervising students on their projects, making sure they stuck to schedule and being there to assist with the work produced.

https://snikfi.wixsite.com/mysite/modual-interact-global

Experience cont.

Academic Project WaterAid

Nov. 2018 - Jan. 2019

UAL & WaterAid collaboration. Brief: design an experience to increase donations through one of the three approaches: educate, activate, or intervene. I designed a 4D immersive room where people could experience the conditions in countries affected by a clean water deficit.

UI/UX Designer & Web Developer Freelance

Aug. 2018 - Sept. 2018

Working in partnership with r0g_, UNESCO and the UN, my professor invited me to work on this project. We investigated how social media was being used during the Anglophone Crisis In Cameroon. My responsibilities included:

- Gathering data using the Facebook Graph API and Facepager
- · Sorting this data into .csv files
- Discovering methods of displaying this data interactively
- · Coding an interactive webpage that displayed the results, using HTML, CSS & Javascript

https://snikfi.wixsite.com/mysite/cameroon

Short Courses

Merit Hardware & Software Program

Jan. 2016 - Mar. 2016

I learnt how to build computers, what the different components of a computer do, such as the motherboard, capacitors, RAM, ROM, hard drives and how to install and change, operating systems.

Skills

Research

Surveys, Screening Surveys, Questionnaires, Interviews, Focus Groups, Observational Studies, Ethnographic Studies, Understanding User Needs, Understanding Stakeholders Needs.

· Ideation and Prototyping

Design of Mobile & Web applications, Interactive prototypes through Figma and code, User Stories & Personas, Storyboarding.

Evaluating and Data Handling

First Click Testing, Tree testing, Gorilla Testing, A/B Testing, Remote User Testing.

Adobe Creative Cloud

Using InDesign to create designed PDFs for project submissions and data analysis results. Designing magazines, posters. Adobe XD to create prototypes of web/app interfaces and sharing them clients.

- Brainstorming
- Critical thinking
- Collaboration
- Experimentation
- Time management
- Leadership
- Prototyping
- Wireframing
- Empathy
- Data analysis
- Adobe InDesign
- Adobe Illustrator
- Abode Photoshop
- Adobe After Effects
- Adobe Premiere Pro
- HTML / CSS
- JavaScript
- · Javascripi
- 3D Printing
- Microsoft Suite
- Marvelous Designer

Languages - English, Albanian & French

- Albanian is my mother tongue. I am fluent in the Gheg dialect.
- I studied French during secondary school, and obtain a GCSE in the language.